妖女前情提要
Previously on Lost Girl...
我们向逝去的海妖致敬
We pay reverence to our departed Siren.
不管谁拿了这种子
Whoever takes this seed
都会拥有Una Mens的综合力量
will have the combined power of the Una Mens.
欢迎来到我的世界 你现在是纯人类了
Welcome to my world, you are 100% human.
你是我们的一员
You are a part of all of us.
解除认领 Bo
Unclaim me Bo.
皇后可不是随便的什么皇后
The Queen doesn't just mean the queen.
Bo 这是说你是那个人
Bo it means you're the one.
战士和皇后之间 必有一死
Between the warrior and the queen, one of the two shall die.
你选了他？
You choose him?
我选了你  你伤透了我的心
I chose you. And you broke my heart.
他们一起会释放黑暗之王
Together they will release the Lord of Darkness.
我的动机是真诚的 但是被囚禁多年
My intentions were true, but years of imprisonment
我的判断力下降 理性被蒙蔽 我就是个傻瓜
weakened my judgment; clouded my reason. I was a fool.
我在我朋友面前说我选了你
I stood in front of my friends and said I choose you!
Rosette是我最忠实的下属 我们深爱对方
Rosette was my most loyal general; we loved one another.
要是他能让她叛变
If he managed to turn her against me...
他让她自己跳进了火坑 Rainer
He made her throw herself into a fire, Rainer!
他到底是谁 Bo
Who is he, Bo?
一个连血王都怕的人
Someone even the Blood King fears.
我父亲操纵了我们所有人
My father manipulated all of us.
我们有一个优势  一个你父亲无法预料的优势
There's one advantage ...one thing your father never could foresee.
我们拥有的感情是真实的 美好的
We share something real.Something good.
Rainer  我是怎么回事?
Rainer.What is happening to me?
我们的标记
Our marks...
不 他的标记
No. His mark.
Bo 不管发生什么事  我们会战斗
Bo, whatever happens, we will fight this.
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  r(st)q
英文字幕：来自互联网
翻译：Neffititi  骷髅头正宫_k
精校：Nef  Joy
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
4x13 - "Dark Horse"
你
You.
你对她干了什么
What have you done to her!
我就知道你不安好心
I knew you were poison.
这句话居然是从拆散无数家庭
This, from the King who separated families,
让孩子眼睁睁看着自己父母被烧死
made children watch their parents burn at the stake
就因为他们不选边的血王嘴里说出来的
if they didn't choose between light and dark!
别说了 求你了 那Pyrripus
Stop... please. The Pyrripus.
你听说过Pyrripus
You've heard of The Pyrripus??
我们遇到了些修女战士 好疯狂的一群人
We ran into these warrior nuns.Lots of white, even more crazy.
Trick  她们崇拜一个马神
Trick, they worship a horse god.
一个恶魔 她们觉得那是我父亲
A demon. They think it's my father.
我们结合是为了破除你的诅咒
We bound to break your curse.
可是我们却把通往地狱的门打开了
Instead we opened the gateway to Hel.
你本不该离开那火车
You should never have left the train.
你就是那始作俑者好么
You're the one who put me there in the first place!
你居然敢违抗血王的法律
You dared to challenge the blood laws!
你究竟要到何时才会对你造成的混乱负责
When will you take responsibility for the chaos you've caused?
你知道你在对谁说话吗
You forget who you're talking to.
我以前就没怕过你 现在也不
I wasn't scared of you then and I'm not scared of you now.
别吵了 我爸可是近在咫尺
Stop! My father's close.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
我能感觉到他
I can feel him.
他在试图过桥
He's trying to cross the bridge.
他要把她弄出来
He's trying to bring her out.
他需要她 Trick
He needs her, Trick.
谁？
Who?
啊
Ah!
黑暗皇后
The Dark Queen.
我
Me.
我早就知道 可我现在需要你告诉我
I've always known this, but now I need you to tell me
有关我血缘的一切
everything you know about my blood.
妈妈 它在燃烧  可我好冷
Mother, it's burning. But I'm so cold.
我空虚寂寞冷
So cold and so hollow.
*西方有关教育儿童的两种理论*
还有那有关先天还是后天之争论的可怕答案
And the horrific answer to the nature/nurture debate.
向来是需要两个人才能制造出一个怪物
It takes both to truly make a monster.
首先是人类 然后是怪物 现在成了神
First a human, then a monster now a god.
一个有圣枝的神
A god with the twig of Zamora...
对 他的能力在变弱
Yeah, whose power is diminishing
现在你把扎莫拉家族最后继承人也杀了
now that you've killed the last Zamoran heir.
真有你的啊 Massimo
Way to go, Massimo, way to go.
你看着
You watch!
你现在唯一成为不朽的机会
Now your only chance at being immortal is someone writing
就是某傻x为你写首口水歌了吧
a shitty pop song about you, hmm?
关于一个坏人如何哭诉他妈妈
About a villain who cries about his Mommy
一个头发变白的坏人
whose hair goes prematurely gray.
等待你的只有坟墓
The only thing awaiting you is this grave.
啊啊啊啊啊
Auugh!
我吞了起源之种  现在这种子要吞噬我
I swallowed the origin seed,and now it's trying to devour me!
那种子可是要六个异种
It took a council of six Fae to keep control
una mens一起才能控制
on the Una Mens power.
人类大脑可就这么点功能了哟 Massimo
The human brain can only take so much, Massimo.
你错了 我现在终于成为我应当成为的人了
You are wrong.I'm finally the man I'm supposed to be.
一个能让我妈骄傲的人
A man who would make my mother proud.
你觉得m女王会觉得骄傲
You think that Evony would be proud of this?
她不要蜜酒也不要种子
She didn't want one mead, nor seed;
不要什么Valkyrie的头发 或者金毛小美人
no Valkyrie hair, no maidens fair.
不等等 她确实要某美女
No, wait. She did want the maiden.
对对 那能行
Yes. Yes, that'll work.
那就是我要给我妈的
That's what we'll bring to Mother...
不
No.
那淫妖的脑袋
the Succubus' head.
我发誓  你父亲的真实身份
I swear,the true identity of your father
我也不曾知晓
remains shrouded from me.
就像你自己的罪恶一样
Much like your own guilt.
够了 现在不是为了小事吵架的时候
Enough.We don't have time for petty bickering.
小事？他杀了成千上万的异种
Petty? He killed thousands of Fae.
我们要不关上那门 更多的人会死去
And more will die if we don't close the gateway.
Trick  我爸
Trick. My father.
血王的女儿袭击了黑暗派
When the Blood King's daughter attacked the Dark,
为了向她母亲复仇的时候  血王被迫做出表率
to avenge her mother's death, the King had to set an example.
以证明他的血之法律绝对可靠
To prove that his blood laws were infallible.
除了把她交给黑暗派我别无选择
I had no choice but to hand her over to the Dark.
Aife是你妈？
Aife is your mother?
我祈祷她会被处刑  可她没有
I prayed she'd be executed. She wasn't.
在黑暗地窖里度过的那些年
All of those years in the black dungeons.
好几百年  他们利用了她
Centuries. They used her.
Aife有我的光明派的血  法师之血
Aife has my Light blood. The blood of a mage.
那能够靠吸取生命存活滋养自己的血
Blood that drains life for nourishment and self survival.
所有异种不都这样
As with all Fae.
可你父亲的血 不管他是谁 它让你
But the blood of your father ...whoever he may be ... allows you
同时吸取多人 更重要的是
to drain life from many victims ...and more importantly,
还能将那生命之力传给你自己之外的人
to transfer that life force to someone other than yourself.
你继承了你父母
You have inherited the abilities
双方的能力
of both your mother and your father.
我的血是混合的？
I have hybrid blood?
我恐怕你的血能让你父亲脱出囚笼
Blood that I fear will help your father escape.
你的血不仅能破除诅咒 还能领导军队
Not only could your blood lift curses,but you could lead armies.
复活战场上死去的人
Resurrect the fallen as they die on the battlefield.
让众人自由
Free the masses.
或者奴役众人 若她被坏人胁迫
Or enslave them, if she's coerced by the wrong hand.
你们这是当我不存在吗
You stop talking about me like I'm not here.
没人能利用我 你们懂吗?
Nobody's going to use me for anything. You understand?
现在怎么办?
So what now?
我们去看看这地狱入口
We check out this portal.
不  不管你父亲是谁 那就是他的目的
No. Whoever your father is, that is what he wants;
要利用你脱出囚牢
for you to be the instrument of escape from his prison.
那你说我们该去哪?
Then where do you suggest I go?
干嘛不来我家 我有你那金发妞
Why not swing by my place?It's where I've got your blonde box.
或者大概说会走路的急救箱更贴切点
Though, she's more of a walking medical kit, really.
你要对Lauren干什么
What the hell do you want with Lauren?
我亲耐的魔法妹 我只要你
Oh my dear Magic Muff: all I want is you,
死在m女王脚下
dead, at the Morrigan's feet.
Kenzi 发生了什么事
Kenzi! What's going on?
到处都是她的血  手机也被扔在一边
Her blood's everywhere, she left her cell phone behind
她明显在黑暗档案馆里找什么东西
and she was obviously looking for something in the Dark Archives.
看看这个
And check this out.
Bo
Bo.
还能有谁
Who else.
那Lauren呢?这发生了什么事?
And Lauren? What happened here?
我不知道
I don't know.
首先 老娘采撷了她的娇花
First of all, I goosed her sweet berries.
就在你坐的那地方
Right where you're sitting.
呕 既生动又混乱
Ew. Graphic and confusing.
我要怎么才能控制这里的温度
How do I control the temperature in here.
上一分钟还巨冷 马上又像棕榈泉那么热了
It's freezing one minute and then summer in Palm Springs the next.
*棕榈泉 地处加州的度假胜地*
异种更年期？
Fae menopause?
*潮热是妇女更年期常见症状*
不 她是人类
No... she's human.
嗷
Ow!
真是不枉我三年的等待啊
I've been waiting three years to do that.
干嘛每个人都要打我
What's with all the punching?!
我终于明白为什么大家都说不要打脸了
I finally get what 'not in the face' means!
你怎么会变人类的
How is it that you are human?
还不是跟那好医生滚床滚的
Champers for the good Doctor and her miracle snatch.
要在平时我让她烧死也就算了 可我儿子把她弄走了
Normally I'd want her incinerated, but my son took her.
我要Lauren  活的
And I need Lauren. Alive.
只有她才能逆转这个过程
She's the only one who can fix... this.
你有个儿子?
You have a son?
是Vex吗?
It is Vex?
要是的话老娘怎么会
As if I'd let him wear that
让他穿那种大龄杀马特的服装
too-old-to-be-goth shit if he was.
是Massimo啦
Massimo.
你特么在逗我?
Are you kidding me?!
我还能说啥  80年代的华尔街就这鬼样子
What can I say, Wall Street in the 80s was totally gnarly.
和一人类春宵一度  就生了这么个怪胎
A weak moment with a human led to birthing an infection.
比特么变种瘟疫还要危险
Who has become more dangerous than a mutating plague.
我亲手把他关在Dal了
I locked him up myself, in the Dal.
Vex把他放跑了
No, Vex let him out.
那小杂种
That little shit.
Massimo会把Lauren带去哪?
Where would Massimo have taken Lauren?
就是他那一不顺心就躲去舔伤口的地方
Where he always goes to lick his wounds when things don't go his way.
他就从来没顺心过 因为他弱爆了
Which they never do,because he totally sucks.
从小就这样 他那小卷毛
Ever since he was a little boy, with his adorable curls
和他的拥抱 恶心
and his... hugs. Ugh.
他想要成为我们的一员
He wanted to be one of us; instead,
他无师自通 看了很多
he taught himself about our ways; surrounded himself with
黑暗派的秘密
the secrets of the Dark.
档案馆
The Archives.
那他现在到底想要什么, Evony?
Then what does he want now, Evony?
那当然是天下男人都想要的我了亲
What all the boys want, darling.Me.
m女王叫你来的
Evony sent you?
不如你给她回个话
Well you give her a message.
老娘恨不能现在就把你碎尸万段
As much as I can't wait to tear you apart
因为你杀了Hale  可我现在忙着
for what you did to Hale, I'm busy dealing with
对付复活的亡灵之军和一个大恶人
a rising army of the dead and a real bad guy.
你真的要让事态恶化吗?
Do you want this to get real bad?
你有没有听说过一种叫雷兽的雷电怪物?
Have you ever heard of a Raiju ...a thunder beast?
*日本传说中随雷电出现的妖怪 形如浣熊有利爪*
我可见过 我还夺走了她的力量
Because I have. And I took this from her.
啊
Ugh!
怎么了bo-bo?是不是有点透支了
What's the matter, Bo-Bo? Looking a little peaked.
你为什么不来把椅子?
Why don't you have a seat?
那种子
The seed.
啊啊
Rrawr!
啊
Ugh!
你从我的保险柜里偷走了种子！
You stole the seed from my vault!
我还整个吞了呢 真是美味
And I swallowed it whole, yum yum.
我来对付这德鲁伊
I'll deal with the Druid!
不 她需要你
No. She'll need you.
这是你欠我的
You owe me this at least!
你特么又是谁?
And who the hell are you?
啊啊啊啊
Aaagh!
告诉那Valkyrie  我的灵魂又属于她了
Tell the Valkyrie. My soul is hers again.
这会很有趣
This is gonna be fun.
我为我做过的一切道歉
I'm sorry. For everything...
不!
No!
天啊  他的预知能力  太强大了
Oh god, his foresight... it's too powerful!
不
No...
他死了
He's gone.
我怎么回来的?
How did I get here?
Trick可是很强的
Trick's stronger than he looks.
他好像给你吃了点药
And he kind of drugged you.
噢 真是好
Oh. Groovy.
他去光明派的图书馆找资料了
He went to the Light Fae library to get some text that
他觉得会有地狱之军的资料
he thinks has information on the soldiers of Hel.
哦天啊 Rainer
Oh god. Rainer.
你好像被狂扁了一顿
You're pretty beat up.
看得出 肋骨断了几根 锁骨也碎了
I figure, a few broken ribs,busted collarbone.
你需要的时候那些靓丽的狐妖医学院妹子在哪啊?
Oh. Where's a hot Kitsune med student when you need one, huh?
Hale  Rainer 我救不了他们
Hale, Rainer.I couldn't save them.
Lauren也被一个我近不了身的傻逼的带走了
And Lauren's been taken by some asshole that I can't even get close to.
我让大家失望了 我不知道该怎么办
I let everybody down.I don't know what to do.
你特么给我闭嘴 好好振作行吗?
Why don't you suck it up and get your shit together?
你说啥?
Excuse me?
当领导好烦  当皇后好讨厌
It sucks to be leader,sucks to be queen
烦死了烦死了烦死了 挺住行吗
it sucks sucks sucks. Get over it!
你该这样跟我说话!
How dare you!
艾玛我好可怜 我是那被选中的人
Oh poor me, I'm the chosen one.
那你干嘛不好好当个选中的人?
Why don't you act like it for once?
你尝起来 不一样了 喜悦
You taste... different. Happy.
等会有的是时间哀悼
There will be time to mourn.Later.
听着 要打败Massimo我还是太弱了
Look, I'm still not strong enough to defeat Massimo.
他现在就是开挂状态  他不会死
He's basically invincible. He won't die.
我们会从试图杀死他的过程里找到乐趣的
But we'll have fun trying to make him.
一而再再而三
Over and over again.
你们还好吧?
You guys okay?
嘿
Hi.
嗨
恩 好尴尬
Well, that was awkward.
世界末日可不就这样 Ben和Liv似的
Armageddon can be. Just ask Ben and Liv.
*指Ben Affleck和Liv Tyler 1998年参演的电影Armageddon *
你要原谅她 肯子 人生苦短
You have to forgive her, Kenz. Life is too short.
是啊我知道 我男朋友刚死 谢谢啊
Yeah, I remember, my  boyfriend just died. Thanks.
Rainer也死了
And Rainer's also dead.
也就是说我有他的灵魂了 还有第二次送它去英灵殿的机会
Which means I have his soul,and a second chance to deliver it
我早该这么干了
where I should have in the first place.
这应该能结束我从英灵殿的放逐
It could end my exile from Valhalla.
恩
Mhm.
那是那小贱人Rosette的东西
That was that bitch Rosette's.
这是挪威语 对吧?
And it's in Norwegian, right?
这个画  大门在火焰中关闭
This drawing. Gates closing over flames.
人们欢呼雀跃  什么意思?
People cheering. What is this?
宜家大甩卖？
A sale at Ikea?
你能翻译这段吗?
Can you translate this part for me?
女儿  心脏
Daughter. Heart.
是说女儿的心能关闭那地狱之门吗?
As in, the daughter's heart will close the portal?
你觉得是说Bo需要掏出她心脏的意思？
Do you think that means Bo's gonna have to rip it out of her chest?
暂时不告诉她吧
Let's not tell Bo.
好
Yet.
先找到Lauren再说
Let's get Lauren first. Okay?
好吧
Okay.
Lauren是头等大事
Lauren comes first.
你爹呢?
And your father?
黑暗爹爹等了三十年才出现
Daddy Darko waited thirty years to show up,
还不能多等一小时吗
he can wait another hour.
救不出Lauren横竖也是个死
We get Lauren, or we get dead.
全力以赴
Whatever it takes.
我倒需要你帮我个忙
I do need something from you though.
哦不是那  我已经吸食了Tamsin了
No, not that, I already fed off Tamsin.
是吗?
Really?
我要是真想打败Massimo
If I'm gonna stand even half a chance at beating Massimo
我就得变回我自己  我需要一个见证人
I need to get back to myself. And I need a witness.
那是你加入黑暗派的契约
That's your Dark Fae contract.
Rainer死的时候带着它...
Rainer had it on him when he...
但他死了 una mens也死了
But now Rainer's dead,the Una Mens are dead,
除了那个该死的没死 人人都死了
everyone's dead except for the guy who should be.
我和黑暗派的联系也该死了
And now so are my ties to the Dark.
Bo 我不觉得这有用
Bo, I don't think that's gonna work.
我是谁可不是写在张纸上就算完了
No piece of paper is going to tell me who I am.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
Rainer曾是我的伴侣
Rainer was my partner;
一个想要结束光明和黑暗争端的人
someone who wanted to end the tyranny between Light and Dark.
他是个好人 Dyson 只不过犯了大错
He was a good man, Dyson, who made a terrible mistake.
我总算知道为什么Hale如此平和了
I see now why Hale was so grounded.
因为他的人生有目标
Because he had a purpose.
我一辈子都在寻找一个国王
All my life I've been searching for a King.
实际上 我该寻找的是女王才对
When what I should have been searching for is a Queen.
我的血是你的
My blood is yours.
我的灵魂和肉体也是你的
My soul. My body.
我向你效忠 Isabeau
I swear fealty to you, Isabeau.
不管你从何而来 是什么样的人
Because no matter where you came from or what made you
我只想永远在你身边
by your side is where I want to be. Forever.
我还以为我们在吵架呢
I kinda thought we were fighting.
之前是的
We kind of were.
我爱你
I love you.
那也就是为什么我希望你和我一起战斗 而不是当我的仆从
And that's why I need you to serve with me, not for me.
不好意思  我们又多发现了点地狱之门的事
Sorry. We found out some more stuff about the portal.
书上说那叫新瓦特桥
Book's calling it the "Cinvat."
*Cinvat  拜火教传说中连接阴间和人界的桥梁*
就在那些疯子拜马教女人圣堂的中心
And it's at the Spiritual Center for crazy pony ladies.
帅哥你怎么说?
So what do you say cowboy?
要去杀点母马不?
Should we break some fillies?
驾驾
Giddy up.
这是个通往阴间的大门
So this is what what a portal to the underworld
看上去是
looks like these days.
是吧  挺明显的
Yeah. It's kinda hard to miss.
马头 旋转木马的碎片
Horse heads, broken bits of carousels.
爹爹可真是戏剧化?
Daddy's got a flair for the drama, huh?
不成功就下地狱好了
Go big or go Hel.
你觉得从那出来的是什么?
What do you think  is coming out of that thing?
大量亡灵吧
Shitload of revenants.
Bo 不要！
Bo, don't!
我是你们的女王  不管你们承认与否 傻x
I am your Queen, whether you swear it or not, fool.
我真正的军队正在路上
And my true army cometh.
我被血所困
I was bound by blood
就让我永远的困在其中
and let it be in it.
人类 异种 都将在我面前低头
Humans, Fae...all will bow before me.
Bo 求你了 回来啊
Bo, come back to me, please!
一切都将在Pyrripus的力量下被摧毁
All will break beneath the  power of the Pyrripus...
Dyson我停不下来
Dyson. I can't stop.
反抗啊
Fight it!
Dyson 你做点什么！
Dyson, do something!
哦 你需要点新技巧
Oh, you need some new moves.
是吗?这不挺好用的
Really?Works every time.
你这是要挑逗我还是要让我扫兴啊
Turning me off  instead of turning me on?
准备好3p了吗?
You ready for a threesome?
你还说我需要新技巧呢
And you think I need new material?
放松
Relax.
你很快就会穿不下你的裤子了
You're gonna wear out your big boy pants.
你这样一笑
You know when you smirk like that
眼周的皱纹可更深了
it really brings out the lines around your eyes.
哦Patrick  你真是既聪明又强大
Oh Patrick. You're as witty as you are powerful.
我们以前怎么没有?
How come we've never... ?
你不是我喜欢的类型
You're not really my type.
因为我是人类？
Because I'm human?
我是个当妈的？
A mother?!
铁石心肠的贱人
A stone cold bitch.
哦艾玛 男人一看到强悍女人
Oh, boo. Bitch is just a word men use
顿感自己渺小的时候 就会叫她们贱人
when they feel threatened by the chick in charge.
我才不会因为自己聪明 有野心道歉呢
I'm not going to apologize for being smart, or ambitious...
那你试图杀死我爱的人怎么说?
Or trying to kill everyone I love?
拜托  你那杀人无数的孙女的爹要真的
Please: if your grand-slaughter's Dad is who
是个你连名字都不能说的人
you're too scared to say he is
我们横竖也是个死
we're all gonna be Bo-be-que'd anyway.
不如找点乐子先
Might as well have a little fun first. Hmm?
肯定还有别的办法
There's got to be another way.
复活兵马俑啊？ 还是去挖沙鲁尔锤？
Resurrect the Terracotta Army?Dig up the Sharur?
*Sharur 美索不达米亚神话中尼努尔塔神的兵器*
要关闭地狱之门只有一个办法
There's only one way to close the gates of Hel
会说话的锤子可办不到
and it's not going to involve a mythical talking mace.
想想吧大爷 这些事情一般都怎么解决
Think old man. How do these things usually work?
往往细小之物才有巨大阴影
Souvent, une petite chose jette une grande ombre.
Sometimes the smallest thing casts the longest shadow.
那我们这是要坐以待毙
So. We just gonna sit here and wait for enslavement
眼睁睁等着混乱来临  因为没酒了
chaos and anarchy? Because we're almost out of booze.
大概吧
Hardly.
呕 这是什么感觉?
Ew. What is that feeling?
你终于做了次正确选择的感觉？
The sense that, for once, you're doing the right thing?
哦  姐的内裤卡臀缝了
Oh...I have a wedgie.
妈呀 当人类真是挫爆了
God! Being human sucks!
但是要是我要出门的话  就得漂漂亮亮的
Still, if I'm gonna go out,I'm going out looking fabulous.
你看上去美如天仙  准备好了吗?
Trust me, you do. Ready for this?
当妈的真是破事一箩筐
A mother's work is never done.
当外祖父的也一样
Neither is a grandfather's.
那可真是有活力
Well that was athletic.
Dyson 那才三个 历史的战场上
Dyson, that was three.How many cursed souls
到底死了多少被诅咒的灵魂?
have died on the battlefields of history?
成百上千万吧
Millions.
那个吻
About that kiss...
我该道歉吗?
Should I say I'm sorry?
为了救了我道歉？
For what, saving me?
你没事吧?
Are you're okay?
我觉得好极了
Yeah. I feel awesome.
Dyson  我父亲在接近  我觉得力量无穷
Dyson, my father is close.I feel so powerful.
你从地狱之门在吸取他的力量
You're channeling his energy through the portal.
你能控制吗?
Can you control it?
或许现在我该疯狂点
Maybe it's time I got  a little out of control.
挺好  她需要你
That's good to hear. Because she needs you.
你居然不跟我说拯救世界在前
You're not going to tell me to save the world
妹子在后?
instead of the girl?
还不都是你教的
You've taught me well.
她也是我的朋友
And she's my friend too.
我爸会不停的从那个门送出亡灵
My father's going to keep sending those things out of the portal
就为了引诱我  我需要你
to try to bait me. I need you to contain
控制那些从新瓦特桥出来的亡灵战士
the dead warriors that  come out of that Cinvat.
别让他们跑去地面上
Do not let them get above ground.
让Tamsin用她的怀疑之力
Have Tamsin cast doubt over them.
让他们自相残杀 把他们撕碎
Make them go at each others' throats. And then tear them out.
当然了  Kenzi怎么办?
With pleasure.And what about Kenzi?
让她在你身边 护她周全
Keep her close. Keep her safe.
你行吗?
Can you do all that?
阻止地狱军队？
Hold off the armies of Hel?
还以为你不会提这要求呢 我的女王
I thought you'd never ask, my Queen.
Kenzi
Kenzi...
你会没事的
You're gonna be fine.
我是m女王的儿子
I am Evony's son.
被活活烧了七天
I was burned alive for seven days.
我绝对可以控制这个流浪者的力量的
I can handle the Wanderer's gift.
你有Rainer的预知能力了？ 你对他干了什么
You have Rainer's foresight? What did you do to him?
痛苦是净化  好痛啊
Pain is a cleanser. So much pain!
你还是痛死吧
I hope you choke on it.
我吸取了异种之力
I have absorbed all things Fae.
你连做梦都想不到的能力
I am knowledge you can only dream of.
你丫就是个纯深井冰卢瑟还脑残
You're a psycho loser with a brain full of shit that
根本就不知道怎么用那些能力
you don't even know how to use.
而且听起来你对原来的种子还过敏
And it sounds like you might be allergic to origin seed.
我有你的肾上腺素测量笔哦
I got your epi-pen right here.
怎么样啊 德鲁伊  长痛不如短痛
What'd ya say, Druid? A little prick to end a big prick?
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
你不应该来的
You shouldn't have come.
我不一直都这样
I always do.
谢天谢地
Thank goddess.
你们这对苦命鸳鸯间的最后悲鸣
Lovers' laments before you both die.
你懂什么叫做爱?
What do you know about love?
我知道妈妈对你很执著
I know that Mother's obsessed with you.
而你对她很执著 天 你不单身还真不容易
And you're obsessed with her. Gee. I wonder why you're single.
她对我苛刻 因为她想让我做到最好
She's hard on me because she wants me to be the best.
我现在牛到爆了
And now I am.
Una Mens可以反射使用任何胆敢挑衅他们的
The Una Mens is able to reflect the power of any Fae
异种的力量
who dared to challenge them.
而我吸取了所有六个人的力量
And I've absorbed all those powers, sixfold.
就跟小叮当的口袋一样 法宝多多
It is a nifty bag of tricks to choose from!
你这个恶魔
You are a monster.
那么我就来给人类贡献一下我最新的把戏吧
Let's start with a tribute to my last kill, as a human.
来自你最爱的海妖的一首短诗
A pretty little ditty from your favorite siren!
啊
Ugh!
Ah!
命运 艾马呀
Destiny. Boo-yah.
停下来 她受够了
Stop it! She's had enough!
你跟我说个毛 她屡败屡战啊
Why you telling me? She's the one who won't quit.
让她走
Let her go.
我喜欢有个观众
I like an audience.
你知不知道你奄奄一息的时候
Do you know you're gonna breathe your dying breath
就要绝望的看着我杀死这位好医生
helpless, watching me kill the good doctor?
你想像力真是多姿多彩
You have a very rich fantasy life.
我可以看见你未来参与的战争
I can see the battle ahead.
这是那个谁的能力 我都已经忘了他的名字了
Courtesy of... I've already forgotten his name.
噢
Ow.
你还好吧?
You okay?
再给我两分钟 我就能脱开手铐了
Two minutes, I'll be out of these cuffs .
真的吗?
Seriously?
我在Kenz的火影神偷训练里学了不少
I learned a lot from Kenzi's shadow thief training.
不仅仅是偷内裤
It's not just about panty removal.
你的前戏总是那么拔尖
Your foreplay was always top notch.
哇 叮叮叮 要来第三场吗
Whew! Ding ding ding! Ready for round three?
先来后到 我们把这个恋母狂杀掉先
First thing's first. Let's kill this motherlover.
不确定的时候 我们就照老规矩来
When in doubt, go with the classics.
哇 你差点整到我
Wow, you almost had me there.
你这风骚容器里肯定加了别的料
Must have a little something extra in the slutty tank today.
没错 这个料叫做末日来袭 傻X
Yeah, it's called the coming apocalypse, dick.
现在 你如果想死得舒坦 我可以考虑考虑
Now, if you'd just die like a good boy, I could get back to dealing with it.
你造吗 你的血统很牛 淫妖
You know...your origins are fascinating, Succubus.
Pyrripus之力
"The power of the Pyrripus".
你知道些什么?
What do you know about it?
我知道被人类养大让你变得软弱
I know that being raised by humans made you soft.
我知道守门人警告你危险来临
I know that the Keeper was right to warn you of the shit
是正确的
that's coming your way.
感到很糟糕 不是吗 Bo Bo?
Feels pretty crappy, doesn't it Bo-Bo?
感觉到无助 当个凡人
Being helpless? Being mortal?
这就是这些年 你的感觉吗?
Is that how you've felt, all these years?
妈妈?!
Mom?!
这不是我和Trick讨论的
This isn't what Trick and I discussed.
不小心误伤
Collateral damage.
看来我又要选择 谁生
Looks like once again ...only I'll choose who lives
谁死了
and who dies.
我从来没见过战场上的女武神
I've never actually seen a Valkyrie in battle before.
令人印象深刻
It's impressive.
你那个护阴袋下面有什么东西值得拼命的吗?
Got anything under that codpiece worth fighting for?
你应该知道
You should know.
这些都是些什么地狱喽罗?
What are these hell spawns?
这只是千万中的一部分
The first of millions.
如果我们不从这里逃出去
If we don't get out of here...
闭嘴!
Shut up!
我只是说说 我们寡不敌众
I'm just saying.  We're outnumbered.
两个人对抗地狱祸害?
Two against the scourges of Hel?
三个
Three.
是时候停止止步过去
Time to stop dwelling in the past
开始修正未来了
and get to fixing the future.
Kenzi在哪?
Where's Kenzi?
她很安全
Safe.
也就现在
For now.
你放她走 不然我把你暴头
You let her go or I blow your bitch brains
脑花溅你女朋友一脸
all over your girlfriend's face.
啊 好吓人 谁教会你恐吓别人的?
Ugh, terrible. Who taught you to threaten?
好吃啊 我打赌人类妈妈尝起来更美味
Yum.  I bet human mommy tastes delicious.
美味 不过我说了可不算
Delectable.  But don't take my word for it.
不准伤害她
Don't you hurt her!
呀 我可以尝到她对你的真实感觉
Ow... I can taste how she really feels about you.
懦夫 可悲 就是个错误
Coward. Pathetic. Mistake.
看到了吗 可以吸气并不是特长
See, it's not sucking chi that makes me special.
特别的是我知道怎么停止
It's that I learned how to stop.
十年来 我杀人狂欢
For ten years, I went on a killing spree.
接着我找到了我的朋友们  你觉得你知道什么叫做爱?
Then I found my friends. You think you know love?
用那个救她
Use it to save her.
去啊 救她
Go on. Save her!
我可以把气送回她身体力
I could breathe the chi back into her.
但是你还没有那个能力 不管你有多在乎
But you don't have that power yet. No matter how much you care.
麻麻
Mommy!
救救她啊
Make it better.
我需要另外一个人的气
I'll need someone else's chi to do that.
一命还一命 异种之道
A life for a life.  That's the Fae way.
你不能伤害我 你不能杀死我
You can't hurt me. You can't kill me.
我有
I've got...
小嫩枝吗?
A tiny twig?
Hale最后的礼物
Hale's last gift.
你以为那个能阻挡我?
You think that's what stopped me?
我对你有别的安排
I've got other plans for you.
哈哈 爸爸就要来了
Well, daddy's coming to play.
你们俩都得死
You're both gonna die anyway.
至少我们能够九泉下合家相聚
At least we'll die a family.
这是你动了Lauren
That is for laying a finger on Lauren.
啊
Augh!
为了雨人哥
For Rainer.
为了小黑
For Hale.
这是为了你伤透了Kenzi的心
And that is for breaking Kenzi's heart.
没事 没事 我在呢
It's okay. It's okay, I got you.
Kenzi 你在这里干什么?
Kenzi!  What are you doing here?
我们等不了那么久啦
We can't wait any longer.
我们寡不敌众 你又受伤了
We're outnumbered and you're injured.
我们必须要抗争 我们得继续打
We have to fight, we have to keep fighting.
我们必须把正门关上
We have to close the portal.
我们不知道怎么
We don't know how...
Dyson 我懂了 这事也有我一份
Dyson, I get it now. I do have a part to play.
你在说么子？
What are you talking about?
命运 总是给我们开残酷的玩笑
Destiny. It has a real sick sense of fun.
唯一的关闭地狱大门的方式
It is the only way to close the gateway to Hel.
Bo的真心
It's Bo's heart.
那就是我
And I'm it.
你戴上了
You wore it...
我喜欢
I love it.
那么雨人?
And Rainer..?
你判断错误了
You were wrong about him.
至少我没看错你
At least I was right about you.
总是这样 从我们第一次见面的时候我就没看错
Always have been, since the first moment we met.
我一直知道你是非同寻常的
And I've always known you were extraordinary.
但现在 一个人类医生可以让异种变凡人?
But now, a human doctor who can turn the Fae mortal?
他们会追捕你的
They're gonna be coming for you.
是吗 让他们试试吧
Yeah? Let 'em try.
你真是黑暗派的
You really are Dark.
不 Bo 我是你的
No Bo. I'm yours.
我们得走了
We have to go.
我的父亲 地狱的大门 Tamsin和 Dyson
My father, portal to Hel, Tamsin and Dyson
还有Kenzi 我的天啊  Kenzi
and Kenzi, oh god, Kenzi...
我得说 Evony情况稳定 而且你知道
I'm going to stay. Evony's stable, and you know...
就是希波克拉底誓言之类的
just Hippocratic oath and all that.
*成为医生宣誓遵守的伦理道德上的规范，如尊重生命 不歧视患者等*
我曰 你是认真的
Shit, you're serious.
你看见她了 就是一个无助的人类
You saw her, all vulnerable and human.
而且多少也是我的错 所以
And I kind of did this to her, so...
很不可思议的事 我还真懂了
Craziest thing of all? I actually get it.
走吧 淫妖 命运在呼唤
Get out of here, Succubus. Destiny's calling.
Dyson  人太多了
Dyson! There's too many!
Bo的心是她的
Bo's heart is her heart!
异种可从来没那么简单
It's never that simple with you Fae!
总是比喻啊 象征啊 Dyson 那就是我
It is always a metaphor, a symbol. Dyson, it's me.
Kenzi 新瓦特桥就是集中的能量
Kenzi, the Cinvat is concentrated energy.
你知道它会对你做什么吗?
Do you know what it will do to you?
Bo是唯一能帮助我们的人  Dyson
Bo's the only one who can help us, Dyson.
而她需要我帮助她
And she needs me to help her!
不 我去
No! I'll go.
不 Dyson
No, Dyson.
她爱你 对 她也爱Lauren
She loves you, yes.  She loves Lauren.
但是你知道我是她的真心 你知道的
But you know that it's me, I'm her heart, you know that.
听着 我有一个计划
Look, I have a plan. Okay?
Rainer有可以预见的能力
Rainer had the gift of foresight.
他知道这些会发生 一定会发生
He knew this would happen ... had to happen.
现在Tamsin拥有他的灵魂 通往英灵殿的金券
Now Tamsin has his soul, the golden ticket to Valhalla.
当这一切结束后 她可以把我带去那里
That's where she'll take me when this is all over,
我会在那里等待
that's where I'll wait.
不
No!
是的Dyson 如果我这样离开 像个战士
Yes, Dyson.   If I go out like this, a warrior.
在战场上 也许我会再见到他
In battle... maybe I'll even get to see him... again...
我会在英灵殿等Bo
I will wait for Bo in Valhalla.
你知道她不会停止找寻我
You know she will never stop looking for me.
她不会放弃来带我回家的
She'll never stop fighting to bring me home.
要出大事了 Pyrripus要来了
Something big is coming. The Pyrripus!
这是唯一的方法 Dyson
It's the only way, Dyson.
这是唯一的Bo拯救世界的方法
It's the only way Bo can save the world!
不 Kenzi 不 不
Oh. Kenzi, no. No.
不 不 不
No, no, no!
Dyson 不 Kenzi
Dyson, no. Kenzi!
英灵殿
Valhalla.
Tamsin
Tamsin!
起来 塔塔
Come on Tammy. Hey hey.
不 你不应该来这里的
No...You shouldn't be here!
但我来了
But I am.
Kenzi
Kenzi...
怎么了?
Yeah?
她离开了
She's gone.
我们会把她带回来的
Hey. We'll get her back.
不 不
No. No!
你不能让Bo找到第二只Hel鞋
You cannot let Bo find the second Hel shoe.
为什么 Tamsin为什么 你看见什么了?
Why, Tamsin, why?  What did you see?
没事的 我会带你离开这里
Hey, it's gonna be okay.  I'm going to get you out of here.
我不会再把你丢下了
I'm not leaving you behind again.
没事的
It's okay.
好了 好了 来吧
There, there. Come on.
我们把Rainer埋在了安可穆尔战场
We buried Rainer near the battlefield at Ancrum Moor.
*Ancrum Moor：1545年苏格兰与英格兰大战的战场之一。*
似乎他应该和那些为他战死的人
It only seemed right that he should rest with those
一起长眠才算对
who fought and died for him.
太多的人牺牲了 生之多艰
There's been too much dying already. It's been hard.
我失去了太多东西
I have lost so much.
但我必须坚强
But I have to be strong.
特别是现在
Now more than ever.
我很想你
I miss you.
我更需要你  我需要你的勇气
But more than that, I need you.  I need your courage.
但我已不再哭泣
But I'm done crying.
不再恐惧
I'm done being scared.
再没有人会在我眼前死去
No one else will die on my watch.
我会不计一切代价 找回你
Whatever it takes, I will get you back.
他们想让我害怕吗?
They want me to be afraid?
应该是他们惧怕
It's them who should be afraid.
我
Of me.